videosolo.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy | VideoSolo

This Privacy Policy of VideoSolo has updated on May 25, 2018, to reflect changes in European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). It applies to the Software, Website (www.videosolo.com), and other interactions (e.g., customer service inquiries), you may have with the Company.

By accessing all the service of VideoSolo, you agree to fully comply with and be bound by the following policy each time. So, please review the following terms carefully.

Q1.

About this Privacy Policy

A1.

VideoSolo is committed to protecting your privacy. And we created this Policy to explain our privacy practices so you will understand what information about you is collected, and how it used and be protected.

Any references in this Policy to "VideoSolo", "we", "our", "us" etc. will be interpreted as a reference to us. A "visitor" is someone who merely browers our website. A "member" is someone who has registered our software. The term "user" and "you/your" is a collective identifier that refers to a visitor, a member or someone who has downloaded our software.

Our contact details can also be found below if you have any comment about our Privacy Policy.

Q2.

What information do we collect?

A2.

We may ask you to provide Personal Information when you:

  * Visit VideoSolo's website
  * Download a software trial or update;
  * Register our products;
  * Subscribe to our newsletters, promotional emails or other materials;
  * Participate in a marketing/sales promotion or an online survey;
  * Contact us, including for sales or technical support.

#1. Personal Data

We may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

  * Email address
  * First name and last name
  * Phone number
  * Order information
  * Payment information
  * Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
  * Cookies and Usage Data

#2. Usage Data

We may also collect information how our Services is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

#3. Tracking & Cookies Data

We use cookies to track the activity on our website and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

  * Session Cookies: We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
  * Preference Cookies: We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
  * Security Cookies: We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

Q3.

How do we collect the information?

A3.

There are numbers of different ways that VideoSolo receives and collects your personal information including:

  * Communications between us
  * Customer Support
  * Email/Direct Mail Campaigns
  * Registration of Products
  * Purchases
  * Surveys

Q4.

What do we use it for?

A4.

VideoSolo may use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * Product Registration: Information you provide upon registration will be used to keep a record of your product to help us provide support to you. VideoSolo also use this information to inform you of product upgrades, new products, promotions or other information that may be of interest to you.
  * Newsletters: We may use your personal information to send you newsletters to provide you with articles and information that we believe may be of interest to you.
  * Internal Analysis: We may use the information you provide us with for our own internal statistical and analytical purposes, to evaluate and profile customers about their preferences and purchasing trends which we may use for marketing purposes and in respect of operations and development.

Q5.

How we protect your personal information?

A5.

We use reasonable precautions to protect your personal information and to store it securely. Sensitive information transmitted to us online is encrypted and is transmitted to us securely. In addition, access to all of our customers'information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted. Only authorized employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. Finally, the servers on which we store personally identifiable information are maintained in a secure environment.

Q6.

Third-Party Analytics

A6.

We may also use third party analytics tools and technologies to track and analyze data from our the Lucid Services. These tools use Cookies to collect information such as how often users visit the Sites, what pages they visit, and what other sites they used prior to coming to the Sites. We use the data collected by such third party analytics tools only to help us administer and improve the quality of the Lucid Services and to analyze Sites and Apps usage. These third parties are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf, except to help us conduct and improve our business. These services collect the IP address assigned to a user on the date the user visits the Sites, rather than a user's name or other personally identifying information. These Cookies cannot be used by anyone at the third-party provider other than to provide these services as described.

Q7.

Links to Other Sites

A7.

Our websites may contain links to other sites. VideoSolo is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each web site to which we may link that may collect personally identifiable information.

Q8.

Children's Privacy

A8.

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

Q9.

Your Rights

A9.

VideoSolo uses, processes, and stores information, as necessary to perform our contract with you, and based on our legitimate interests in order to provide the Products and Services. We rely on your consent to process information to send promotional emails and to place cookies on your devices. In some cases, VideoSolo may process Personal Data pursuant to the legal obligation or to protect your vital interests or those of another person.

Individuals located in the European Economic Area (EEA) have certain rights in respect to their personal information, including the right to access, correct, or delete information we process through your use of the Sites, and/or Products. If you're a user based in the EEA, you can:

  * Have your information corrected or deleted. You may ask us to correct information you think is inaccurate or completely delete all information that we hold about you by emailing:[support@videosolo.com](mailto:support@videosolo.com).
  * Access your personal data report by submitting a request at [support@videosolo.com](mailto:support@videosolo.com). This report will include the information we have about you, provided to you in a structured, commonly used, and portable format.
  * Object to us processing your personal data. It is your right to lodge an objection to the processing of your personal data by emailing: [support@videosolo.com](mailto:support@videosolo.com) if you feel the "ground relating to your particular situation" apply. The only reasons we will be able to deny your request is if we can show compelling legitimate grounds for the processing, which override your interest, rights, and freedoms, or the processing is for the establishment, exercise or defence of a legal claim.
  * You can ask us to stop using your information, including when we use your personal data to send you marketing emails. We only send marketing communications to users located in the EEA with your prior consent, and you may withdraw your consent at any time by clicking the "unsubscribe" link found within VideoSolo emails and changing your contact preferences. Please note you will continue to receive transactional messages related to our Products, even if you unsubscribe from marketing emails.
  * Complain to a regulator. If you're based in the EEA and think that we haven't complied with data protection laws, you have a right to lodge a complaint with your local supervisory authority.

Q10.

Updates to Privacy Policy

A10.

This privacy policy was last updated on 25 May 2018 as required to the GDPR laws.

We will occasionally update this privacy policy to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. If there are material updates to this policy or in how VideoSolo will use your personal information, we will notify you by posting a notice of such an update on the privacy policy link prior to implementing the change. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy policy to be informed of how VideoSolo is protecting your information.

Q11.

Contact Us

A11.

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [support@videosolo.com](mailto:support@videosolo.com).
